hello this is Arty marage from ethys
Fair bringing you yet another ethy cast
in this episode which places a spotlight
on our asia-pacific community will
feature insights from E Chen Yap who is
the lead for ethics at credential
Assurance company in Singapore a
longtime member of our Bella Asia
Pacific chapter in this conversation
iching will share some fun ideas and
also insights on how they continue to
embed ethics into what they do every day
so stay tuned to this conversation
coming right
up welcome back and it is my pleasure to
be here with iching on eicas iching has
led credential Assurance company
Singapore's ethics team since 2021 and
in the past three years the team has
done a lot of work to make the ethics to
make sure that ethics remains top of
mind to all employees iching thank you
so much for being here with us
today hi ATI thank you for having having
me today so let's kick off the
conversation the virtual background
you're using it isn't just an ordinary
background I'm sure there's some meaning
to it can you share a bit more about
this and how it has become a
programmatic theme at credential
Singapore sure thank you RTI um in
changing world of business trust and
integrity are critical these concepts
are often discussed but their real
presence remains philosophical so we
explore ethics and its impact on
corporate reputation and have been
emphasizing the need for of ethics for a
long time in credential Singapore ethics
is an important value everyone needs to
have and we really wanted to put a face
to it so I thought about it one night
how can I make ethics come to life and
came a UA moment um we then conducted a
companywide design competition invited
corporate employees and financial
representatives to participate and they
came up with these fantastic designs of
our mascot so I do a quick introduction
eth as our lead mascot she's the face of
do right eth the elephant embodies
integrity and courage in doing what is
right even when no one is looking was
born on Global Ethics dat 2021 and she
leads our other ethics companion trusty
and shortcut as we continue to do right
by each other and all our stakeholders
because we know what happens in the dark
will come to light next we have trusty
is our sociable dolphin who thrives in
environment where there is high trust
amongst his teammates he enjoys working
together to achieve common ethical goal
not forgetting the cutest of them all
shortcut the crab he a playful but
impatient mascot who likes to take
shortcut Etho and truste believe that
it's of Paramount importance for one to
learn from his mistakes and not repeat
them therefore they support shortcut
through his ethical journey and together
our ethics mascot are popular teammates
in Prudential Singapore to promote an
ethical culture their presence remind
everyone to always do
right I certainly like all the mascots
and I hope to meet them one day for sure
and I love the idea of Tates in the
ethics arena in fact you have another
concept at credential Singapore that has
a collaborative theme to it you call it
the ethics advisor program what exactly
is the ethics advisor program sure I'd
like to share more as well ethics is
important in credential Singapore for
instance there is an ethics and
sustainability Comm Community checked by
our CEO the ethics team conducts
training for all employees and financial
reps through divisional engagement and
emerence sessions we have put in place
different types of Ethics resources
available to our employees we raise
awareness and Foster strong ethics
culture in prenal Singapore through
ongoing ethics engagement events and
display collaterals so that we feel
Ethics in our physical space and these
mascots and collaterals serve as visual
reminders to always do right and of
course place is a team of Ethics
advisers that you mentioned they play
crucial role in credential Singapore and
they are part of the community that
provides a listening ear and guides
individuals to the right resources our
EAS encourage colleagues to make ethical
decisions and our EA help to shape
ethics culture and events whilst Jud
with their day-to-day job it's truly the
art of collaboration which helps to re
reinforce the ethical culture in
credential Singapore we assemble
individuals from all divisions with
different backgrounds experience years
of service and seniority so that all
vises is
represented so you have certainly laid
it all out for us there eaching now we
know what the Ethics program advisor is
about um could you share a a little bit
more about what inspired it and what are
the end
goals definitely um in prenal Singapore
we recognize the importance of ethical
consideration in various aspects of work
it is inspired by Design to Foster
responsible
behavior promote moral values and
address ethical dilemas we aim to create
a supportive environment where
individuals can discuss and navigate
through ethical issues Al ultimately
contributing to an elevated level of
ethical awareness and a responsible
workplace one of the goals of the
program is to cultivate a culture of
ethical behavior and decision making
among our employees by fostering open
communication and awareness between the
EAS and other members of the team we aim
to create an environment where ethical
considerations are integral to the
decision making process thereby
promoting Integrity trust and
responsible conduct throughout the
organization uh besides that we also
observed several incidental benefits
such as one stronger team EAS come
together share their learning
opportunities observations amongst other
contributions which will help to
cultivate a sense of close need
community that further promotes the
exchange of ideas to person development
we equi our EAS with resources for them
to play their roles
effectively um the planning and rolling
out of cross functional collaborations
is not rare but certainly cherished with
more exposures and cross functional
collaborations it could Aid our EAS in
the future roles where skill sets of
conflict management stakeholder
collaboration and project management
could come in handy three confidence
building credential Singapore wants to
create a positive work environment where
employees Envision fulfilling Futures
and making a difference the EA program
leads a solid foundation that goes
beyond policies and processes it
includes our very own colleagues and
peers in the journey who continually
build confidence while discharging their
responsibility as our
EAS and that is certainly inspirational
those three elements that you've
highlighted um and I know our viewers
will find this concept interesting um
and they probably want to know how do
you train ethics advisors and what does
that communication look
like sure um very simply put um the
training the process of training doesn't
stop nor does it only apply to our EAS
uh while we conduct curated divisional
trainings our EAS are equipped with a
variety of engag ments as well uh for
starters the onboarding of new EA's
kickoff with the induction program we
share specific roles and
responsibilities real life sanitized
cases amongst other key details
subsequently our EAS continue to come
together and collectively chart our
journey for this year is important that
uh every EA contributes effectively and
within their scope of time um available
as we are mindful of the existing work
commitments uh therefore a series of
activities are launched for the entire
year which could be inperson engagement
catch UPS or some conducted virtually
that helps with creating a more
effective and convenient options for our
colleagues uh besides familiarizing EAS
with stakeholders and available
resources in the company we also aim to
engage them for divisional training
sessions this exposure further connects
ethics in that division through the EA
bridging uh regularly the EAS also
promotes ethics newsletter quizzes
contest and activities and help to
inject consistent but fun elements in
doing right and building off that eing
of course no program is complete with
some without some metrics attached to it
could you share a few of the accomplish
ments that you and your team have
experienced since kicking off the
program certainly um there are few key
elements which I like to share um number
one transparency and accountability
credential Singapore is transparent
about our ethical guidelines policies
and ethical decision making and often
hold our staff accountable for decisions
we make to inclusivity and diversity and
effective ethics program considers
diverse perspective is crucial to
involve people from various backgrounds
cultures and experiences to avoid
biasness and promote fairness number
three continuous refinement ethics is
not Statics it evolves with societal
changes real life examples and
guidelines we need to stay informed
learn from past missteps and adapt our
programs accordingly for do WR reporting
we encourage employees to report
unethical Behavior without the fear of
retaliation hence retaliation in itself
is a form of misconduct and this is
emphasized time and again stakeholders
engagement engage with all stakeholders
to understand their concerns and
incorporate their feedback into our
Improvement and training six ethical
leaderships leaders play a pivotal role
in setting the tone for ethical Behavior
we have supportive Ethics Committee that
sets clear guidelines and their actions
and commitment to ethical values
influence the entire
organization along with these elements
we notice increased participation levels
for ethics activities and events along
with improving ethical culture survey
responses our EA greatly Aid in drumming
up conversations around these activities
which help Foster an ethical culture in
credential Singapore I'd like to
highlight that an effective Ethics
program isn't just implementing a set of
rules is a commitment of dedicated
individuals to spreading what's right
even when no one is
looking and that's such an important
point that you rais um to build off that
I'm guessing being a part of this
program is certainly my demand is there
a limit to how many or who can
participate in essence how do you select
employees for this
program we don't have a limit to the
number of EAS uh for this program but uh
at a back of our minds we think raise R
Ace in the selection process for our
ethics advisors our representation we do
try our best to ensure a healthy mix of
and employees of different job grade
function demographic to ensure diversity
and inclusion wherever possible a
aptitude and EA serve as a volunteer
Ambassador for the Ethics program hence
a healthy work life balance for
colleagues is important EAS must first
be comfortable with Theo appointment and
are coping with their respective Baus
before embarking as an EA C contri
contribution the willingness and
attitude determines the quality of
contribution of our EAS the actual
discharging of their responsibility and
contribution will be considered no
better big or small and E engagement to
actively engage with colleagues in their
division and across presedential
Singapore EAS are encouraged to share
their observations learning during
catchup sessions or an ad hog basis with
the team so that we could timely assist
the relevant party of concern whilst the
race concept serve as a guide for our EA
selection process We Believe above all
our EAS should embody good ethical
practices in their daily work and that
in itself is a huge
Advantage each and year certainly
providing so much strong insights I I
want this conversation to go on and on
for a very long time but I know we're
we're heading towards the end of of our
conversation but before we go are there
any closing thoughts or elements you
would like to highlight to our
audience um certainly um today we shared
essential components of our ethics focus
in credential Singapore and as we
conclude I like to emphasize our
commitment to fostering a culture of
trust and integrity ethics is not just
set of rules it's a guide fiding light
that shapes our decision our journey
towards a more ethical organization
begins with each one of us the strength
of ethical Foundation lies in the daily
choices we make the conversations we
engage in and the examples we set
credential Singapore will continue to do
right even when no one is
looking with that iching given what
we've discussed today you and your team
have certainly charted out a strong path
forward to continue this important
conversation we look forward to seeing
what's ahead and learn more about the
future of this program for everyone
tuning in and you just heard from ich
Ching Yap lead ethics at credential
Assurance company Singapore